var jsonDevelopment = `{
  "id": 103,
  "title": "Development",
  "clues": [{
      "id": 4000,
      "answer": "fetus",
      "question": "An unborn baby horse",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 103,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 4001,
      "answer": "Milk Teeth",
      "question": "The name of the temporary teeth of a foal",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 103,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 4002,
      "answer": "Filly",
      "question": "A female horse under 3 years of age.",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 103,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 4003,
      "answer": "Colostrum",
      "question": "The name of the mare's first milk",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 103,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 4004,
      "answer": "11 months",
      "question": "The length of time for the gestation of a horse",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 103,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 4005,
      "answer": "Suckling",
      "question": "Term for a horse that has not been weened yet",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 103,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 4006,
      "answer": "Dam",
      "question": "Term used for an equine's mother",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 103,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 4007,
      "answer": "Colt",
      "question": "A male horse under 3 years of age",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 103,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 4008,
      "answer": "Foal",
      "question": "A horse of either sex less than one year of age",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 103,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    },{
      "id": 4009,
      "answer": "Yearling",
      "question": "a horse of either sex between the ages of one and two",
      "value": 100,
      "airdate": null,
      "category_id": 103,
      "game_id": null,
      "invalid_count": null
    }
  ]
}`;
